(whispering "Maggie-lo")
(singing)
You step up, swing it on the first green
Drive straight down like a laser beam
Confidence drive they've never seen
But I know how this will go
Ball's in the bunker on whole tree
Still you smile like it's old routine
You line it up, you play it clean
Never cheat or let it roll
Straight shooter who can't shoot straight
You never won, never hesitate
Chocolate strokes put you on your fate
You tee it up, but you won't escape
I watch the score climb with the sun
We're way past par, but having fun
Hit the water, you never run
It's a magic valley where
Fork put, freeze and rump that bite
Still you laugh through every slice
No like is no secret, right?
Sponge to a fold, I swear
Straight shooter who can't shoot straight
You never won, never hesitate
You tee it up, but you won't escape
Could've kicked it out, but that's not you
Counting every swing, no matter true or screwed
You score card, looks like modern art
But you play around with an honest heart
Straight shooter who can't shoot straight
You never won, never hesitate
Chocolate strokes put you on your fate
You tee it up, but you won't escape
Still you smile through every hole
A legend with a bougie soul
Can't shoot straight, but it makes you whole